Guide to the Records of the Vice President and Deputy Chancellor and Senior Vice President, Debra James 1980-2000 RG.6.1.1
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of the Vice President and Deputy Chancellor and Senior Vice President (Debra James)
1980-2000
New York University Archives
James, Debra, 1953-2000
RG.6.1.1
26 Linear Feet 26 linear feet (26 boxes)
This collection contains the administrative records of Debra James in her capacity as Vice President and Deputy Chancellor, and Senior Vice President.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged topically.
The files are grouped into 1 series: Topical Files
Related Material at the New York University Archives
L. Jay Oliva Records
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains the administrative records of Debra James in her capacity as Vice President and Deputy Chancellor and Senior Vice President.
Historical/Biographical Note
A native of Bayonne, New Jersey, Debra James earned her B.A. and M.A. degrees at NYU and took her first job as an administrative assistant to then-Chancellor Sidney Borowitz. Over the years she succeeded to positions of increasing responsibility, serving as Director of Admissions, Assistant Chancellor, Associate Chancellor, and a Vice President, always working closely with deans of the schools and with University chancellors and presidents.
In 1998 she was appointed one of the University's three senior vice presidents. In this role, James fulfilled major responsibilities across a broad range of University activities and programs. However, she was principally distinguished by a personal approach to her duties that made her an admired figure among students, faculty, staff, and University friends and neighbors. In all her undertakings, she sought to connect members of the NYU family and foster a spirit of community throughout the University.
The areas under her leadership included the Office of Student Affairs, the Office of Commencement and Special Events, the Faculty Resource Network, the President's C-Team, and the Office of Community Service. She also had vital roles in the establishment and growth of NYU's America Reads program, the Africana Studies Program, and the Asian Pacific American Studies Program. She also had significant involvement in the development of the University's study abroad programs and in the La Pietra site in particular, where she cultivated strong and cordial personal ties between NYU and the Florentine community. She also oversaw the development of the University's new faculty and staff dining venue, The Torch Club.
James died in 2000.
Sources:
James, Debra, Biographical File, New York University Archives.
Access Restrictions
Institutional records of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation (the date on which each document was written). Board of Trustees records are similarly closed for 35 years from the date of creation. The opening date for files spanning several years will be 20 years from the most recent date. Access will be given to material already 20 years old contained within a collection that is not yet open when such material can be isolated from the rest of the collection.
Materials related to personnel, faculty grievances, job searches and all files with information that falls under the University's Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) policy are permanently restricted.
Please contact the University Archivists with specific questions regarding restrictions.
Provenance
This collection was transferred to the University Archives in multiple accessions from 1998-2000 from the Vice President and Deputy Chancellor and Senior Vice President's office.
Memorandums.; Universities and Colleges -- Administration; Correspondence.; Reports.; James, Debra, 1953-2000; New York University. Office of the Senior Vice President; New York University; New York University. Office of the Chancellor
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Search Firm Info, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General note
    Barcode #: 3 1142 042266547
  - FAS Search, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226654 7
  - Wagner Interview Sch., undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Jodie Allen, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mary Jo Bane, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Benjamin R. Barber, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Davis Bobrow, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jo Ivey Bouford, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Review Libraries, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - FAS Annual Planning Report, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Wagner Dean Search Robert Berne, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Wagner Dean Search, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Wagner School Dean Search, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Search Firm Info, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Law Deans Review Debra James, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Trustees Pres, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Special Planning Trustees, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Trustees Pres, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting Financial Affairs Committee, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Searches, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Stern Dean's Review Debra James, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226655 4
  - Confidential Background Info, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Patricia S. Schroeder, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Norman Steisel, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Catherine Stimpson, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Vietnamese President, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Richard Celeste, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dall W. Forsethe, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - William W. Ginsburg, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Margaret A. Hamberg, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Signature- Approval C-Team, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - VP Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - VP Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - VP Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Thrift Shop--Debra James, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Community Service--Debra James, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - National Service--Debra James, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226656 2
  - Language Arts, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - General NYU Information, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - November 9th Senate Meeting Debra James, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dr. Mona Michail, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square Speakers, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Barbara Hendra, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Russian Tea Room Lectures, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Rectors 2, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Personal, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Ireland House Dedication, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Letter to the University Community, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Themes, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ernst & Young, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Domestic Partner Benefits, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - C-Team, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Call Log Records, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - DJ Themes General, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Barbara Sporn, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Paris/Athens Trip, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Childcare Taskforce, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Financial Aid, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rector's Conference--University Response to Criticism, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence--Elizabeth, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Housing Taskforce, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226657 0
  - Housing Taskforce, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Hall, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cantor Film Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Cantor Film Center, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cantor Film Center Dedication, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cantor Film Center Dedication, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - S. Baruch, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Check Presentation, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - L. Berlowitz Budgets, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Leslie Berlowitz, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Leslie--Transition, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Atlanta Trip, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Ancient Studies Dinner, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Ancient Studies, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Albany Day, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Action Grants, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Action Grants Review, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Greeting Cards--Christmas, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Action Grants--Review, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Council Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Council Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Meetings (binder), 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226338 7
  - Dean's Meetings (binder), 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Inauguration of L. Jay Oliva (binder contains 4-17), 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Dean's Meetings (binder), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Untitled Binder (study group), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Vice Presidents' Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226339 5
  - Dean's Meetings Academic Year, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Meetings Academic year, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - F.S. Fitzgerald, Virginia Woolf & Oscar Wilde, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Citibank Stint, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226350 2
  - Citibank Stint, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Citibank Stint, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Citibank Stint, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Citibank Stint, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Check Stubs, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Citibank Deposit Slips, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Various Check Requests, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Various Check Requests, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Various Check Requests, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Various Check Requests, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Various Check Requests, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Various Check Requests, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Various Check Requests, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Four Way, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Garden State, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Korean Convocation, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Yeronisos Island, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Metro Call--Check Requests, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Metro Call--Statements, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Bernard Hodes Advertising Inc., undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Lloyd Burlingame, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Ancient Studies, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - David Brontheim Memorial Sevrice, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Ballroom Chair, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Unveiling of Brademas Portrait, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Oct, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Nov, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Dec, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Barbara Egypt--CVs for Associate, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Carol Ann Banks, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Dental Search, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Debra James Hughes, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Wood Furniture, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Year End Summary, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Year End Summary, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Chatfield, Dean, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Peter Chill, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - FAS, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - FAS Minutes, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - FAS Staffing and Planning, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - FAS, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Four Way, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Kriser Dinner Proposal, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226340 3
  - AMC, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Black Renaissance/Black Noir, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - French Legion Honor, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Duncan Rice, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Italian American Student Club Reception, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - ABAFS, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - AMA, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Susan Greenbaum Reception--invitations, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Susan Greenbaum Reception--emails, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Susan Greenbaum Reception--guest list, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Susan Greenbaum Reception--RSVPs, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Kaufman Retirement Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Russ Hamberger, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Dinner Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dean's Cuisine Breakfast, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Caribbean Barbeque--FRN, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - LJO's thank you speeches, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Alum and Faculty Club Meeting, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Kriser Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Marsha Harris Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Give a Violet Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 8th Graduating Class of MLK Scholars, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Service Recognition Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Assocation of Black Faculty Administration and Staff Luncheon--Community Fund, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Assocation of Black Faculty Administration and Staff Luncheon--Guest List, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Assocation of Black Faculty Administration and Staff Luncheon--Invitations, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Assocation of Black Faculty Administration and Staff Luncheon--Emails, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Assocation of Black Faculty Administration and Staff Luncheon--RSVPs, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Council Dinner, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - 25-Year Service Award Breakfast, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Provincetown Playhouse Dedication Ceremony, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - ABFS Luncheon--Memos, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - ABFS Luncheon--Invitations, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - ABFS Luncheon--Emails, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - ABFS Luncheon--RSVPs, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Stern School Undergraduate Pre-Commencement, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - TSOA Salutes the Graduating Class of 1998 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - School of Education Doctoral Convocation, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Medical School Last Day Exercises, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Thank You Reception--Invitation, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Thank You Reception--RSVPs, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Thank You Reception--Dbase and Labels, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Thank You Reception--Email, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Musical Theatre Project, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - American Management Assocation, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Africana Studies Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Briefing Materials for Africana Studies Faculty Authors Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Doctor Oliva's Surprise Party, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Maya Lin Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Tyran's Farewell Party, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Faculty Council Reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Briefing for the Summer Celebration at the Penthouse, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Luncheon Honoring the Nuptials of R. Calhoun and J. Johnson--J.Johnson and R. Calhoun's luncheon, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Luncheon Honoring the Nuptials of R. Calhoun and J. Johnson--invitation, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Luncheon Honoring the Nuptials of R. Calhoun and J. Johnson--emails, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Luncheon Honoring the Nuptials of R. Calhoun and J. Johnson--guest list, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Luncheon Honoring the Nuptials of R. Calhoun and J. Johnson--RSVP list, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Luncheon Honoring the Nuptials of R. Calhoun and J. Johnson--lunch reception, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Beginning of Year Divisional Luncheon, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Glover Dinner, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Dave Finney, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Autumn Babies Briefing, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - C-Team Holiday Reception, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Thanksgiving Reception Dinner, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Thanksgiving Reception, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Edelman Reception, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Guidance Counselor Reception, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Luncheon Keynote Facing the Jobs Challenge, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Briefing for Donna's Party, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Maurice Greenberg Reception, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - President's Holiday Party, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Holiday Party for Student Leaders, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - All-University Holiday Sing, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Graduate Deans Meeting, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - AAU Community Service, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Christmas Luncheon, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Thank You Party List, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - GEI Luncheon, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Janet and Barry, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - TSOA Reception, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - C. Duncan Rice, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226341 1
  - C-Team Directors Luncheon, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Community Service Reception, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Sir Harold Acton, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - ABAFS, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Dental Candidates--Dr. Michael Alfano, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Dental Candidates--Mr. H. Garland Hershey Jr., undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Dental Candidates--Dr. Steven F. Bergen, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Dental Candidates--Dr. Neil A. Demby, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dental Candidates--Geral Kugal DMD, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Dental Candidates--Dr. Harry G. Meeker, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dental Candidates--Dr. David A. Nash, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Dental Candidates--Dr. Fouko Suhonen, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dental Candidates--Dr. Edward P. Trimmier, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Dental Candidates--Barry Richard Rifkin, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Dental Candidates--Christopher Winks, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Dental Candidates--Christopher Winks, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Dental Candidates--Dr. Mark Wolff, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Dental Search--Dean and Elizabeth, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Chiara Battistello, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Calendar Changes--October, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Calendar Changes--September, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Calendar Changes--August, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Calendar Changes--July, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Calendar Changes--July, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Calendar Changes--June, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Calendar Changes--May, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Calendar Changes--April, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Calendar Changes--March, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Calendar Changes--February, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Calendar Changes--January, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Cambridge, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - AMA Courses, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - AMA, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - State of the University Dinner, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Gallatin Dean Search Candidates--Gallatin Dean Search, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Gallatin Dean Search Candidates--Steven Diner, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Gallatin Dean Search Candidates--Beatrice Banu, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Gallatin Dean Search Candidates--Suzanne Woods, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Gallatin Dean Search Candidates--E. Francis White, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Gallatin Dean Search Candidates--Francis E. White, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Gallatin Dean Search Candidates--Paul Rosenberg, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Carligle with Naomi and Lillian Vernon, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Anna D. Smith, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226342 9
  - Andrew Spielman, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Aromatherapy, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Artist-N-Residence, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Auditors Notes, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Relations Conference, Greenwich, CT, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Admissions Video, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Alain Coblence, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Anita Kerman Gulkin, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 10th Anniversary Celebration of Neural Science, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Barbara D. Gunn, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Michelle O'Connor, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Michelle O'Connor, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Brademas Apartment, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - BHCF Educational Center, Inc., 1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - BCCC--The Black Community Crusade for Children, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - BCCC--The Black Community Crusade for Children, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - BCCC--The Black Community Crusade for Children, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Bunny Grossinger, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Carlos Flores, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - NSEE Quarterly, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Colleen Stevens, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Collette Tabeek, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - C-Team Advisory Board Meeting, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - C-Team Director's Meeting, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Campus Contact, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Campus Media, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Community Service, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - New York University Faculty and Staff Assistance Program--Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Donna Boguslav, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - David J. Maurrasse, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Effective Business Writing, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Dorothy Durkin, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Disneyland--Check Requests, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Dorothy Ng, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Financial System Redesign Project, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - FSAP, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - FSAP Advisory Board, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Gloria King Allen, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Harper's Session, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Joy Bauer, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Jill Claster, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Judson Hall, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - J. O'Conor, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Jeffrey Barea, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - K. Noelle Deihl-Harteveld, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Main Building, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Kaufman Reception, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Keirsey and Bates, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Multimedia Center, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226343 7
  - Million Man March, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Michelle O'Connor, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - MacCracken Dinner, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Michael Green, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Mazda, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Monte's, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - National Crosstalk, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - New Rochelle, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - OWWA Dinner, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - OSL, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - OISS, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Otesaga Hotel, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - OWAA Luncheon, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Oasis/NIA Awards--Selection Committee, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Peninsula, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Polytech Aud. Report, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Ponce and Flores, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Professor Gute, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Parks, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Patricia Hynes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - R. Riley, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Red Burns, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Rudin Awards, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Rosie O'Donnell, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Sabrina, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Soho Sanctuary, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Sports Matters, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Senator Jack Reed, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Sue Turk, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Stefano Scafetta, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Santa Claus Operation, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Sheila Lukins, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Fresh Air Fund, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Ulric Haynes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Vicky London, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Virgil Renzulli, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 37)